const questions3 = [
    {
      question: "What is the concern popularly felt by the people over the fourth industrial revolution?",
      options: ["Many jobs are at risk of extinction", "All workers will become equal", "A few new jobs will be created"],
      answer: 0
    },
    {
      question: "What suggestion does the technical giant Elon Musk give regarding AI?",
      options: ["Adopt AI in all fields", "Things will be done faster by AI and therefore it is very useful", "Tight regulation must be had for the use of AI"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      question: " What is the need of the hour in the of the 'loss of jobs' on a large scale?",
      options: ["look for other jobs in agriculture", "Do vigorous reskilling and training for the challenge of new jobs", ".save money and sit idle"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "'Breaking silos' means",
      options: ["Integrating various disciplines of study to have a holistic development", "Treating each branch of knowledge as a unit in itself"],
      answer: 0
    },
    {
      question: "The word 'disrupted' means...",
      options: ["A minor difference", "A drastic change", "An emergency situation"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "What does the underlined word in the sentence 'firstly, we must realign india's education system to emphasise skills rather than mere degrees' mean?",
      options: ["readjust", "go along the same line", "unorganized"],
      answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "Choose the two ways that state how 'socail media ' should be used.",
        options: ["To spread sensational but fake information", "To respect elders in the society", "To share reliable information", "To not share very personal information"],
        answer: 3||4
      },
      {
        question: "Why was it considered impossible for the computer to defeat a human in the game 'GO' a couple of years ago?",
        options: ["Because the computer is a fool", "Because of the number of moves the game involved", "Because it is difficult to programme a computer to play games"],
        answer: 1
      },
      {
        question: "What suggestion does the technical giant Bill Gates give regarding AI?",
        options: ["Robots need to be taxed to compensate for greater efficiency", " Things will be done faster by Al and therefore it is very useful", "Robots must be used in every field of human activity"],
        answer: 0
      },
      {
        question: "What must be done to have jobs?",
        options: ["Look for other jobs in agriculture", "Do vigorous reskilling and training for the challenge of new jobs", "Save money and sit idle"],
        answer: 1
      },
];

export default questions3;